What can you find out about a guy during
the combine that lets you know that
he'll be a good addition to what you
already have going? Yeah, I would say
just poise under pressure. Uh this isn't
the easiest atmosphere and situation to
present yourself and and talk about what
your beliefs are and and review your
college career. Uh you got a room full
of GMs, head coaches, coordinators that
are asking tough questions. With some of
these guys you can tell their heartbeat
never really gets picked up. They're
very comfortable, they're very secure in
who they are. This might be the first
time you start talking to some of these
guys, but if they become a Chicago Bear,
this is just the beginning of a constant
dialogue to come. How do you use your
identity and your background to help
facilitate those meaningful
relationships with the players? Yeah,
this is where it all starts. Um I think
when these players enter the interview
room and present themselves,
um you get a little feel for who they
are. Is this Is this an individual that
fits our culture, our building,
um that's going to be part of what we're
building? And and I think it's just a
starting point, but I love this step to
to build that relationship, talk to
Roquan and Caleb about their time when
they were coming through the room. You
remember those moments and it just
builds off of that. You're going to be
making some life-changing calls. I know
how much that means to the athlete, but
talk to me about the gravity of that
moment from your perspective and how
much that means to you. Yeah, we take it
really uh personal, you know, because
you are a part of their journey. Um you
get to see them grow up. Um our
background starts when when they're in
high school and then going through
college and we're following and tracking
uh every move that they have, um getting
to know their family, their backgrounds.
Um and once you make that selection,
they're part of your family, uh the
Bears family. So, we take a lot of
responsibility, a lot of, you know, joy
in seeing those guys start at the very
bottom as rookies and building up
through their career, turning into
second, you know, contracts and helping
us win championships. So, you're part of
their journey, they're part of yours, um
and to see them grow, I think back in my
time, you know, before Chicago, seeing
those guys walk in and then seeing them
become superstars. Like it's it's just a
very rewarding process. And you went
from a college O-lineman to now help
running an organization that has a black
president, a black quarterback, and a
black GM. Have you considered at all the
legacy you're creating and not just the
Bears' immediate impact, but for your
family or other people looking up to
you? Absolutely. I think about it every
single day. Um talked to Kevin about it
a lot. Um there's an opportunity to
influence a lot of different people.
There's an opportunity to give other
people the opportunity to kind of see
our journey and how we operate. Um and
you want to open up doors for others, um
so that they can, you know, model their
career after you uh or Kevin,
uh and and really help them achieve
their goals. So, I think about it every
day. It's something I take a lot of
pride in.
Um I know as an organization we take a
lot of pride in that as well.